<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infrastructure on Tom Saleeba (TechoTom)</title>
    <link>/categories/Infrastructure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infrastructure on Tom Saleeba (TechoTom)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 05:37:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/Infrastructure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maven deploy to Sonatype Nexus &#34;401 Premission Denied&#34; workaround</title>
      <link>/post/2012-12-24-maven-deploy-401-workaround/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 05:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2012-12-24-maven-deploy-401-workaround/</guid>
      <description>My current infrastructure has an instance of Jenkins as the Continuous Integration server and Sonatype Nexus as the repository manager. The POMs for my project and the settings.xml file for maven are configured so that Jenkins can automatically deploy SNAPSHOTs to the Nexus repository but the problem arose when I had a build that went to production and I needed to deploy that pre-built artifact to Nexus&amp;rsquo; RELEASE repository. This was easier that going back and checking out the correct versions of the many dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blacklisting a module on Ubuntu Server 11.10 Oneiric Ocelot</title>
      <link>/post/2012-05-21-blacklisting-a-module-on-ubuntu-server-11-10-oneiric-ocelot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 11:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2012-05-21-blacklisting-a-module-on-ubuntu-server-11-10-oneiric-ocelot/</guid>
      <description>This assumes you have vim (the command line text editor) installed. If not, you can use vi or any command line text editor in its place.
 Change to the modprobe directory: cd /etc/modprobe  We need to create a new blacklist file to store our blacklistings in. If there are already other files in this directory, you can reuse one of them but for the sake of separating configuration you&amp;rsquo;ve made from the out-of-the-box setup, we&amp;rsquo;ll create a new file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XenServer 5.6.1 FP1: Mounting a guest VM&#39;s hard drive (VDI) on the host</title>
      <link>/post/2012-05-21-xenserver-5-6-1-fp1-mounting-a-guest-vms-hard-drive-vdi-on-the-host/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 10:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2012-05-21-xenserver-5-6-1-fp1-mounting-a-guest-vms-hard-drive-vdi-on-the-host/</guid>
      <description>Back story This is a problem that I ran up against because I was running the host machine as a bare host and all the functionality that I needed was in the guest machine. The purpose of this was to insulate myself from changes in hardware and to be able to easily backup the entire server (the guest) so it could be restored from image. This meant that occasionally I&amp;rsquo;d need to access files on the guest machine&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;hard drive&amp;rdquo; but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t running so methods that require networking were out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>